Guide to the Kent State Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- James Munves papers, 1970-1981; Series IV
  - Legal
    - Federal rules of evidence (Box 1)
    - Gag rule of Judge Young, also contains documents relative to Rosen's attempt to overturn rule (Box 1)
    - Hammond v Brown, civil suit brought by Scribner to overturn report of special grand jury (Brown was Ohio att'y general) (Box 1)
    - Jencks Act, instrumental in rendering access to Justice Dept. and other investigatory materials, grand jury reports, etc, made available to defense in Kr v Rh (Box 1)
    - Jury selection (Box 1)
    - Justice Dept., mostly on efforts to obtain federal grand jury (Box 1)
    - Kr v Rh appeal to US Supreme Court in 1974; at which plaintiffs obtained right to have civil trial (Box 1)
    - Ex-parte Milligam, landmark martial law case (Box 1)
    - Monroe v Paper, landmark case under civil section fed civ rts act (1983) on right to sue law enforcement officers (Box 1)
    - Morgan v Hevth, civil suit by ACLU against illegal search of KSU dormitories following shootings (Box 1)
    - Ohio law and responsibility (Box 1)
    - Pre-trial, conferences with Judge Young 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - Rhodes, legality of order sending ONG to Kent, paper by Engdahl (Box 1)
    - Scheuer v Rh (Box 1)
    - Schroder v Richardson, attempt to force convening of fed grand jury (Richardson was A.G., US) (Box 1)
    - Summation of Joseph Kelner in Kr v Rh (Box 1)
    - Tape and photo index, Kr v Rh (Box 1)
    - Trial (Kr v Rh, 1975) May, newsclips (Box 1)
    - Trial (Kr v Rh, 1975) June, newsclips (Box 1)
    - Trial (Kr v Rh, 1975) July, newsclips (Box 1)
    - Trial (Kr v Rh, 1975) August, newsclips (Box 1)
    - Trial (Kr v Rh, 1975) index to transcript (Box 1)
    - Defendants Canterbury, Rhodes; Witnesses Delaney, Montgomery (Box 1)
    - Defendant Del Corso (Box 1)
    - Defendant Shafer (Box 1)
    - Shooters (Box 1)
    - Defendant Rhodes (Box 1)
    - Defendant J. R. Snyder (Box 1)
    - Witness Stiegmeier (Box 1)
    - Trial summaries, from newspapers (Box 1)
    - Verdict comments (Box 1)
    - Judge Don Young (Box 1)
    - Appeal briefs after Kr v Rh verdict (Box 1)
    - Appeal, hearing, 6th Circuit, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Second trial, Kr v Rh, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and memos, Kr v Rh, 1978 (Box 1)
  - General
    - Algiers Hotel incident in Detroit, abuse of police power (Box 2)
    - Berkeley, California shooting incident, abuse of police power (Box 2)
    - Fred Hampton murder, Chicago, abuse of police power (Box 2)
    - Orangeburg, S.C., abuse of police power (Box 2)
    - Riots and civil rights (includes massacre in Mex. City) (Box 2)
    - Riots in Ohio (Box 2)
    - ACLU, includes new releases issued by Ohio branch (Box 2)
    - Brochure, Artists for Justice, fund-raising for plaintiffs (Box 2)
    - President Carter and KSU shootings (Box 2)
    - Geography and Demography (Box 2)
    - J Kelner paper on KS shootings (Box 2)
    - KSU (Box 2)
    - Professor Jerry Lewis (KSU) papers on shootings (Box 2)
    - "Mary" newsclip (Box 2)
    - J. A. Michener (Box 2)
    - May 1970 aftermath of shootings (Box 2)
    - National Guard, articles on; includes summary of testimony at Kr v Rh (Box 2)
    - New York Times indices related to shootings (Box 2)
    - Terry Norman (Box 2)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
    - ROTC fire (Box 2)
    - Scranton Commission, Pres. Nixon lr to Gov Scranton (Box 2)
    - Spirit of the 1960s, press comments (Box 2)
    - Victims (Box 2)
    - Robert White, pres KSU, Time Mag. article (Box 2)
    - Stephen Young, former US Sen., Ohio, letters, etc disputing others on shootings (Box 2)
    - Miscellany, includes xerox copies of documents relating to shootings (Box 2)
    - More miscellany (Box 2)
  - Notebook with tan cover marked K.S. #2, Circa 1970-1975 (Box 2)
    Notebook is paged and has table of contents inside front cover; among other items it contains lists of the Kent State cases (civil and criminal cases arising out of the shootings) and of other legal cases concerning issues raised by KS shootings. It also contains day-by-day chronology of events related to the shootings, from January 1, 1970 to October 30, 1975.
  - Notebook with yellow cover, marked K.S. #2 (Box 2)
    Contains notes of interview with Steven A. Sindell (SAS), lawyer who represented many of the KS plaintiffs; also notes on Judge Battisti, Tom Grace, Benson Wolman, Steven Keller (para-legal), interview with Chris Jindra (Cleveland Plain Dealer Reporter) (all but Battisti based on interviews).
  - Envelope, labelled Env. 1 (Box 2)
    Contains documents relating to attorneys' dispute over Judge Thomas' award of legal fees and expenses as part of out of court settlement of Krause v Rhodes.
  - Notes on plaintiffs and defendants in Krause v Rhodes (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Kent State material: copies of documents in evidence at trial (Box 2)
  - Reprint from Cleveland; biography of Benson Wolman (ACLU) (Box 2)
    See also the interview with Wolman in this Series, Box 1.
  - A-1: Criminal Case, US v Shafer
    - Transcript, 1974 October 29 (Box 2)
    - Notes on opposite cases (Box 2)
    - Xerox copy of US Code 18:242 with references (Box 2)
    - Summary, US v Shafer (Box 2)
    - Screws v US, landmark case under this section (18:242), criminal section, civil rights act (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous material on trial, omitted from book (The Kent State Coverup) (Box 2)
  - A-2: Articles, press releases, etc.
    - Press release, UC Dept of Justice, 1971 August 31 (Box 2)
    - Letter, Sen. S. Young to General Stewart, 1971 August 16 (Box 2)
    - James Michener commencement address, KSU, 1970 December 9 (Box 2)
    - American Report, 1971 November 12 (Box 2)
    - Guardsman's letter, Akron Beacon-Journal, 18 August 1971 (Box 2)
    - Letter, J. Adams to Sen. S. Young, 1971 December 3 (Box 2)
    - Press clipping, Cleveland Plain Dealer, Sen. Young's reply to Michener, 1971 15 December (Box 2)
    - Article by Walter Cronkite from "Eye on the World" (Box 2)
    - Press clipping, New York Times, 5/3/78, Nixon Memoirs (Box 2)
    - New Yorker piece on Kent State by Phil Hamburger, 1971 June 5 (Box 2)
    - Good Housekeeping piece, October 1970 (Box 2)
    - Press clipping, New York Times, 1970 May 6 (Box 2)
    - Ladies Home Journal piece, October 1970 (Box 2)
    - Press clipping, New York Times, 1971 May 19 (Box 2)
    - Akron Beacon-Journal special supplement on Kent State, 1970 May 24 (Box 2)
  - A-3
    - FBI reports on deaths of Schroeder, Miller, and other hospital admissions, including guardsmen (Box 2)
    - Engdahl notes on possible perjury by Gov. Rhodes (Box 2)
    - Transcript, Krause v Rhodes, Delaney testimony (Box 2)
    - Prof. Jerry Lewis (KSU) paper on Ohio Special Grand Jury, excerpts (Box 2)
    - KSU faculty Senate report on Ohio Special Grand Jury, excerpts, 1971 February 1 (Box 2)
    - Transcripts, ACLU taped interviews with KSU students (Box 2)
  - A-4
    - "Minority Report of the Commission on Kent State University Violence," 1970: electrostatic copy of typescript with annotations (Box 2)
  - Manuscript materials, early drafts of The Kent State Coverup, deleted pages, etc., containing matter not included in published version of the book (Box 2)
  - Manuscript (Box 3)
- Additional donors, 1970-1981; Series V
  See also material from additional donors in various accessions.
  - Family of Allison Krause
    - Letters received from the public, 1970-1974 (Box 1)
  - Helen Myrick
    - KSU faculty minutes and other circulars, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Newspapers, posters, clippings, and other printed matter, 1970, 1974-1979 (Box 2)
  - James Gregory Payne
    - Resumé, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Dissertation, "A Rhetorical Analysis of Selected Interpretations of the May 1970 Kent State Incident", 1977 (Box 3)
    - Occidental College presentation of Kent State: A Wake and Kent State: A Requiem, 1978-1980, undated (Box 3)
      - Electrostatic copies of correspondence, press releases, reviews, and student papers (Box 3)
      - Posters, programs, photographs, cassette recording (Box 3)
    - Kent State: The Movie, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
      - Call sheet, cast list, memoranda, shooting notes, promotional flyer (Box 3)
      - T-shirt (Box 3)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1972-1980, undated (Box 3)
    - Photographs: Payne, Bill Wenger, Undated (Box 3)
    - Paper, "Historical Accuracy Versus Dramatic License in Television Docu-Drama: The Making of 'Kent State'", 1981 (Box 3)
  - Mary Vincent
    - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 4)
    - Newsletters and newspaper clippings, 1971-1980 (Box 4)
    - Minutes and reports of KSU student organizations, 1970-1978 (Box 4)
    - Circulars describing the Center for Peaceful Change, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
    - Other printed matter, 1976-1979 (Box 4)
    - Portion of petition, Undated (Box 4)
    - Map (hand drawn) of demonstration site, Undated (Box 4)
    - Electrostatic copies, including pp. 14-15, of KSU student government minutes, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Statement supporting May 4th Task Force, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Brief in U.S. Court of Appeals case, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Introduction to KSU President Brage Golding, 1977 (Box 4)
    - TLS, William Kunstler to colleagues, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Larry Jansen (husband of Lesley Wischmann)
    - Photographs of KSU, copies, Undated (Box 4)
      Existence and Location of Originals
      Original photographs were returned to Larry Jansen after copying.
  - William Gaffney
    - Photographs and slides of his model of the site of the shootings, Undated (Box 4)
    - Model (Box 1–5)
      Access to the model itself requires permission in advance from the Director of Manuscripts and Archives. The model is stored at the off-site Library Shelving Facility in five boxes and measures 50 cubic feet when assembled.
  - Emil Dansker
    - Audio tape and videotape cassette of a documentary, "Kent: Covering the Confrontation," WBGU-TV, Bowling Green, OH, 1970 (Box 4)
  - J. Gregory Payne
    - Kent State: A Requiem [video recording], Circa 1981
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Added 7 Sep 1983.
      - Original (Box 5)
        Restricted
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 5-D)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 5U)
- Additional material, 1971; Accession 1982-M-016
  Received from Paul Keane, 1981.
  See also Series II. Paul Keane Papers and Accessions 1990-M-047 and 2006-M-115.
  Access to materials in this accession requires the permission of Paul Keane until May 4, 2020.
  - Signed petitions and other material relating to the petition drive to convince President Richard Nixon to convene a Grand Jury to investigate the Kent State shootings, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1-13)
    - Additional material (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
- Additional material, 1977-1980; Accession 1983-M-008
  Received from Timothy Viezer, 1982.
  - Daily Kent Stater, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1-9)
  - Daily Kent Stater, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Clippings from various publications, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Additional material, 1967-1982; Accession 1983-M-017
  Received from J. Gregory Payne, 1983.
  - Movie materials
    - Correspondence, tributes, 1976-1981 (Box 1)
    - Other materials, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Clippings [electrostatic copies], 1979-1981 (Box 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1971-1981 (Box 1)
    - Original chronology, Undated (Box 1)
    - Photographs, scripts with revisions, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Photographs, 1980, undated (Box 1)
    - Photographs from movie and play, Undated (Box 1)
    - Reactions to the movie [2 folders], 1973-1981 (Box 1)
    - Related research [2 folders], 1980, undated (Box 1)
    - Research notes, 1977, undated (Box 1)
    - Research notes [electrostatic copies], Undated (Box 1)
    - Phone book -Alabama, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Scripts, revisions, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Speeches, related research materials, 1974-1977, undated (Box 1)
  - Original research
    - Correspondence, 1967-1982 (Box 1)
    - Legal and historical research, 1970-1981 (Box 1)
    - Interviews, 1970-1981 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1980, undated (Box 1)
    - Pictures/Photographs, Undated (Box 1)
  - Newspaper articles
    - Daily Kent Stater [4 folders], 1970-1980 (Box 2)
    - Newspapers, 1973-1980 (Box 2)
    - Clippings [2 folders], 1970-1980, undated (Box 2)
  - Dissertation material
    - Original research, 1981, undated (Box 2)
    - Dissertation material, Undated (Box 2)
    - Manuscript: Mayday: Kent State, Undated (Box 2)
    - Original manuscript of thesis [2 folders], Undated (Box 2)
  - Materials and Manuscript for Mayday: Kent State
    - Research, 1980, undated (Box 3)
    - Photographs [electrostatic copies], Undated (Box 3)
    - Interviews, Undated (Box 3)
    - Permissions package, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
    - Original drafts, Undated (Box 3)
  - Kent State: A Requiem (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1980, undated (Box 3)
    - Materials for the play, 1975-1980, undated (Box 3)
    - Scripts [4 copies], Undated (Box 3)
  - Manuscripts, 1970-1980, undated (Box 3)
  - Notes, 1970-1980, undated (Box 3)
  - Poetry, Undated (Box 3)
  - Kent State Jackson State Memorial Forum recordings, University of Illinois, 1974
    Includes speeches by Peter Davies, Hugh Munro, Dean Kahler, Arthur Krause, and Florence Schroeder.
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - Part 1, 1 (Box 5)
    - Part 2, 1 (Box 6)
    - Part 3: Florence Schroeder regarding Bill Schroeder, 1 (Box 7)
    - Kent State special and parents, 1 (Box 8)
    - ITV S168, 1 (Box 9)
  - Kent State video tape projects, University of Illinois, 1974
    - Payne tape 1, 1 (Box 10)
    - Tape 2, aud. 1, D, Sony - Rover, 1974-10-15; 1 (Box 11)
    - Tape 3, aud. 2, E, Sony - Rover, 1974-10-15; 1 (Box 12)
    - Tape 4, aud. 3, F, Sony - Rover, 1974-10-15; 1 (Box 13)
    - Tape 6, press conference, B, Sony - Rover, 1974-10-15; 1 (Box 14)
      Includes a note stating "End of press conference beginning of D[?]town evening activities."
    - Tape 7, Quad, A, Sony - Rover, 1974-10-15; 1 (Box 15)
    - Unidentified tape, 1 (Box 16)
    - Role playing, 1974 Fall; 1 (Box 17)
    - Role playing, 1974 Fall; 1 (Box 18)
  - Posters, Circa 1980 (Box 4)
- Additional material, 1970-1979; Accession 1987-M-096
  Received from James Munves, 1987.
  See also Series IV. James Munves Papers.
  - Briefs-Court of Appeals (Box 1)
  - Court of Appeals-Appendix (Box 1)
  - Briefs-Supreme Court, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Briefs-Supreme Court, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Manuscript notes with index of transcript (Box 1)
  - "Kent State" teleplay by Gerald Green (Box 1)
  - "Kent State" teleplay-revision, 1980 (Box 1)
  - "Kent State" teleplay-third draft, 1980 (Box 1)
  - "Kent State" teleplay-fourth draft, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Kent State Coverup, correspondence, illustrations, and galley proofs, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, documents, and notes, 1970-1979 (Box 1)
- Additional material, 1975; Accession 1987-M-097
  Received from Robert and Joseph Kelner, 1987.
  - Transcript-Krause vs. Rhodes, 1975
    - Vol. 1- Vol. 14 (Box 1)
    - Vol. 15-Vol. 29 (Box 2)
    - Vol. 30- Vol. 44 (Box 3)
    - Vol. 45-Vol. 53 (Box 4)
  - Voir dire of the Jury-Krause vs. Rhodes, 1975
    - Vol. I-Vol. IV (Box 4)
  - Voir Dire of the Jury-Krause vs. Rhodes pp. 165B-165T? (Box 4)
  - Deposition of Edward King-Krause vs. Rhodes, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Audiocassettes
    - Joseph Kelner Kent State Summation (3 tapes) (Box 4)
    - Rhodes-Taft debate (1 tape) (Box 4)
- Additional material, 1968-1982; Accession 1989-M-048
  Received from David E. Engdahl, 1989.
  The accession consists of the records of David E. Engdahl, attorney on the legal team for plaintiffs in the civil suits that arose from the shooting incidents at Kent State University, May 4, 1970. The bulk of the records pertain to Krause et al. v. Rhodes et al. and related cases, which were in litigation from 1970 to 1981. The case was tried twice, first in 1975 and finally in 1978. A settlement was reached in 1979, but there were subsequent appeals related to the payment of attorney's fees and the protective order issued in 1976. These appeals were tried in 1981. In addition to motions, orders, and correspondence with the court, the records include correspondence among counsel, news clippings, notes, and background materials. Engdahl collected and attempted to publish poems commemorating the deaths at Kent State, which are included in the accession.
  Of particular interest to researchers are the extensive photographic documentation that Engdahl compiled on behalf of the plaintiffs and the testimony, memoranda, and motions related to the use of photographs as evidence. Several photographers served as witnesses in the trials, and a great deal of testimony was oriented around photographs and maps.
  The accession is arranged under seven headings: Legal, Background Materials, General Correspondence, Clippings, Photographs, Audiotapes, and Poetry.
  The Legal files are mainly related to Krause et al. v. Rhodes et al., but contain records for other cases directly related or topically relevant to the events at Kent State University. Records pertaining to Krause et al. v. Rhodes et al. are organized in chronological order. Other cases are organized in rough chronological order.
  The Background Materials are arranged alphabetically in six sections. Biographical background materials contain notes, clippings and other materials about defendants, witnesses, and jurors collected by Engdahl in preparation for trials. Reports contain background materials prepared by agencies, expert witnesses or individuals and presented as such. Topical background files contain notes, clippings, and other materials organized alphabetically by topic. The witness testimony index is a collation of testimonies, depositions, interviews, and statements from various sources. Writings are mostly Engdahl's, but also contain drafts from other writers.
  General Correspondence is organized alphabetically by correspondent and topic. Much of this correspondence relates to legal strategy, relations among plaintiffs and counsel, and public relations surrounding the trials. Correspondence with the court is generally filed with legal papers. Most correspondence regarding poetry and photography is filed with those materials rather than in general correspondence.
  Clippings are organized topically and then chronologically.
  Photographs are organized by format. Engdahl gathered reprints from many photographers who witnessed the events of May 4. He collated these into the plaintiffs' exhibits, juxtaposed to photographer perspective maps. Engdahl also assembled and organized the photographs in sequence to show the chronology of events on May 4 (boxes 51-52). Many of these photographs are published elsewhere, but the collection contains a significant number of photographs that have not been widely distributed.
  - Legal
    - Krause et al. v. Rhodes et al. (Box 4)
      - Docket sheets, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Background memoranda, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
      - Motions, memos, orders, miscellanea, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 15)
      - Motions, memos, orders, miscellanea, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 16 - 18)
      - Counsel selection controversy
        - New York City meeting, 1974 November (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Motions, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Pretrial conferences, orders, pleadings, notes, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22 - 29)
      - Depositions
        - Notices of depositions, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
        - Deposition testimony and exhibits, Circa 1975 (Box 3, Folder 31 - 37)
        - Designation of deposition testimony, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Docket sheets, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Documentary discovery, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 40 - 42)
      - Jury, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 43 - 48)
      - Motions, memos, orders, miscellanea, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 49 - 66)
      - Notes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Motions, memos, orders, miscellanea
        - General, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 68 - 75)
        - Engdahl memoranda on photographs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Closing argument, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Verdicts, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 78 - 80)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 81 - 82)
      - Notice of Appeal, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Motions [summary judgement], 1975 (Box 6, Folder 84 - 95)
      - Synthesis of testimony index, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 96 - 101)
      - Motions, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 102)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 103)
      - Motions and miscellanea
        - Pending Sixth Circuit Court decision, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 104 - 107)
        - Costs, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 108)
        - Photographic evidence, 1975-1978, undated (Box 8, Folder 109)
        - FBI report, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 110)
      - Notes on exhibits, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - Memoranda, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 112 - 121)
      - In-house memoranda, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 122)
      - Sixth Circuit Court
        - Briefs, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 123 - 127)
        - Certiorari, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 128 - 130)
        - Opinion, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 131)
        - Draft brief, Undated (Box 11, Folder 132 - 133)
        - Bound appendices
          - Volume 1: Litigation Documents, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 134)
          - Volume 2: Transcript, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 135)
          - Volume 3: Transcript, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 136)
          - Volume 4: Transcript, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 137)
          - Volume 5: Transcript, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 138)
          - Volume 6: Transcript, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 139)
          - Volume 7: Transcript, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 140)
          - Volume 8: Transcript, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 141)
          - Volume 9: Exhibits, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 142)
          - Volume 10: Photographs, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 143)
          - Volume 12: Testimony and Exhibits, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 144)
      - Motions and miscellanea, 1976-1977, undated (Box 14, Folder 145 - 153)
      - Pleadings
        - Protective Order, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 154 - 157)
        - Kent State Gymnasium, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 158 - 162)
      - Discovery, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 163 - 164)
      - Miscellanea, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 165 - 169)
      - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 170 - 174)
      - Exhibits, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 175 - 177)
      - Interrogatories, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 178 - 179)
      - Memoranda and miscellanea, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 180 - 182)
      - Motions on Abell film, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 183)
      - Pleadings
        - Pretrial, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 184 - 185)
        - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 186 - 194)
      - Recusal and judge designation, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 195)
      - Jury, Circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 196 - 197)
      - Protective order, 1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 198)
      - Settlement, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 199)
      - Transcript of pretrial proceedings, 1978 October 13 (Box 18, Folder 200)
      - Trial proceedings [five volumes], 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 201 - 206)
      - Notes and miscellanea, Undated (Box 20, Folder 207 - 211)
      - Settlement
        - Orders, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 212 - 213)
        - Protective order, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 214 - 216)
        - Pleading file index, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 217)
        - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 218)
        - Filings, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 219)
      - Post-settlement appeals